twobrightlights.com 2012-06-08

# Two Bright Lights: Privacy - Online Publicity Platform

## privacy policy

Updated on March 2, 2012  
Two Bright Lights is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy tells you about our online collection, use and disclosure of personal information. The terms of this policy apply to all personal information collected by Two Bright Lights on the website Two Bright Lights.com. We have created this policy pursuant to the Personal Property Protection Act.

This site is operated by Two Bright Lights. For personal information protection purposes, Two Bright Lights is the controller and, unless otherwise noted, is also the processor of the personal information. Information collected may be retained as long as it is reasonably required for the purposes it was collected.

Two Bright Lights is based, and this web site is hosted, in the United States of America. If you are from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law and you register an account on the website, visit the website or otherwise use the website, please note that any personally identifiable information that you provide to Two Bright Lights will be transferred to the United States. Any such personally identifiable information provided will be processed and stored in the United States by Two Bright Lights or a service provider acting on its behalf. By providing your personally identifiable information, you hereby specifically and expressly consent to such transfer and processing and the uses and disclosures set forth herein.

##### Consent to Collection of Your Personal Information

When you visit this site, certain kinds of non-personal information, your IP address and access times, may be collected automatically as part of the site's operation. We also may collect navigational information, including information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions taken in connection with the site.

We only collect personal information about you after you have provided us with your consent to collect that specific information. By voluntarily providing this information to us, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as set out in this privacy policy.

##### Registration

Two Bright Lights does not require you register or provide personally identifiable information in order to use and access the public website. However, if you register, to access the software service, you may receive access to additional features, and the more detailed the information you provide in the registration section of the website, the better you may customize your website experience. If you choose to register a user account in order to take full advantage of the software service, Two Bright Lights may request certain information (such as your name and e-mail address) in order to provide you with the communications you request and customize its contact with you. Two Bright Lights may also use the registration information you provide for other purposes with your consent.

##### Personal information includes: 

  * Information collected when you register including your member name and password, your name, your mailing address, email address, and phone number.
  * Information collected when you make a purchase including your credit card number and billing address.

##### Use of Your Personal Information

Two Bright Lights collects and uses your personal information to:

  * Create and manage your membership account;
  * Process your transactions;
  * Provide customer service;
  * Perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies, and those of our trusted partners and affiliates;
  * To run Interactive Areas;
  * To communicate with you about your transactions, new products and services. 
  * We may send transaction-related communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, and purchase confirmations.

##### Personal Information Provided as Part of Testimonials

If you provide comments, feedback, information or materials regarding the website, content or Two Bright Lightsacute; products (collectively, "Testimonialsquot;) and you include your personally identifiable information as part of the Testimonials, such information may be made available to any parties using the website and/or such Testimonials. If you do not wish to have your personally identifiable information made available in this manner, you must remove any such information from the Testimonials before providing them to Two Bright Lights. Two Bright Lights is not liable for any damages caused or incurred due to personally identifiable information made available in the foregoing manner.

##### Disclosing Your Personal Information

Except as set out in this privacy policy, Two Bright Lights does not disclose or sell your personal information to any third-parties.

We may disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order) or with requests of law enforcement authorities; to enforce or apply this privacy policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our customers' rights, property or safety; to protect our customers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, Two Bright Lights; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay. In addition, information about our customers, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing or sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of our business assets.

We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our Service.

We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve Two Bright Lights (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of our features). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this policy. As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Amazon's S3 storage service to store some of your information (for example, your Files). You can find more information on Amazon's data security from the S3 site or, read more about how Two Bright Lights and Amazon securely store data.

##### Accessing Your Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire to receive non-account specific information from Two Bright Lights, Two Bright Lights will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update and/or remove your previously-provided personal data. This can be done by emailing a request to Two Bright Lights at [support@twobrightlights.com](mailto:support@twobrightlights.com). You can change your preferences for follow-up contacts by Two Bright Lights. If youacute;re registered with this site, you can change the information you´ve provided to us in the registration section of the site. If you prefer, you can cancel your registration altogether. Email us if you wish to take this action. Additionally, you may request access to the personally identifiable information as collected by Two Bright Lights by sending a request to Two Bright Lights as set forth above. Please note that in certain circumstances, Two Bright Lights may not be able to completely remove your information from its systems. For example, Two Bright Lights may retain your personal information for legitimate business purposes, if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, for account recovery purposes, if required by law or as retained in Two Bright Lightsacute; data backup systems or cached or archived pages. All retained personally identifiable information will continue to be subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy to which you have previously agreed.

If you would like to review or revise information that you previously provided to us, you may access and change your personal information in the "My Account" section of the site. You may also contact Customer Service by email at [support@twobrightlights.com](mailto:support@twobrightlights.com) for assistance.

##### Use of Cookies and Other Technologies

Two Bright Lights uses "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive. Cookies contain information, including personal information, which can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit, your registration information, session identification number and your navigational history and preferences.

Cookies offer you many conveniences. They allow us to identify registered users when they return to the site so that they can retrieve previous image search results, access lightboxes and view their previous invoices. Cookies also save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information.

In some cases, our third-party service providers may use cookies on our sites. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Two Bright Lights only, and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies but you will be able to perform basic navigation through the site.

##### Security of Your Personal Information

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to help protect your personal information including without limitation:

  * Limiting access to your personal information to those of our employees who require it to provide services to you;
  * Requiring employees to sign confidentiality agreements to protect customer and other confidential information;
  * Ensuring that third-party service providers sign confidentiality agreements to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and not to use it for any unauthorized purposes;
  * Encrypting credit card information on our order forms using secure socket layer (SSL) technology; and
  * Storing your personal information in secure computer systems which protect it from unauthorized access or use.

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If a password is used to protect your account and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential.

##### Email Referrals

If you choose to use our email referral services to tell a friend about our products or services we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will use that information to send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the site and review the product or service you have selected. We may use a third-party provider to administer this function, but any such third-party provider may only use the information submitted to facilitate this email.

##### Children

We do not intend to solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13 without parental consent. If you are under 13, you shall not use or enter information on this site, including without limitation, any Interactive Areas of the site without parental consent. Please contact Customer Services by email at [support@twobrightlights.com](mailto:support@twobrightlights.com), to obtain the necessary parental consent forms.

##### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users that are residents of California to request certain information regarding Two Bright Lightsacute; disclosures of personally identifiable information to third parties for such third partiesacute; direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please email Two Bright Lights at [privacy@twobrightlights.com](mailto:privacy@twobrightlights.com).

##### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. When we make changes, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the policy. If there are material changes to this statement or in how Two Bright Lights will use your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes here or on our home page, or by sending you an email. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit one of our sites.
